

JOHN CARLO H. ABENALES

COMPUTER SCIENCE UNDERGRAD

CONTACT INFORMATION

Cellphone No. : 0915 098 1097 Email : abenalesjc11@gmail.com Address : 2641 INT 38 PASIG LINE STA ANA MANILA

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a 4th year student at Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Maynila aiming to show the utilization of my skills and knowledge in order to fit in for industry level jobs, record every experience and add every knowledge and information that I will obtain, utilize any acquired skills, experiences, and knowledge.

COMPUTER RELATED SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Average of 70 wpm typing speed
- Adept data mining skills
- Adept Python programming
- Adept C and C++ programming
- Adept Java programming
- Adept Web Related Scripting (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Microsoft Office

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptive and Flexible
- Ability to work under pressure
- Fast Learner
- Proficient Analytical and Logical thinking
- Reliable problem-solving skills
- Proficient verbal and written communication skills

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

January 2018 - February 2019

ITech Global - IT Position, On the job training

June 2019 - August 2019

T-Mobile - Account, Sales, and Troubleshooting Expert, Costumer Service Representative

July 2021 - August 2021

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Maynila - Full Stack Developer, On the job training

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

College

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Maynila

- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science
- Full College scholarship as a PLM student granted by the city of Manila

Senior High School Paco Catholic School

- Science and Technology, Engineering and Mathematics (STEM) Strand
- Achiever Award
- Math Club Member

Junior High School Paco Catholic School

- Sipnayan Competitor
- Math Club Member
- Computer Society Member

PORTFOLIO

- LookBack Application: A Covid 19 Contact Tracing and Notification System
- Automata Project: J4CK Compiler

CURRENT PROJECTS

- **System for Software Engineering:** Puppy Love Dog Adoption Application
- Thesis Title Proposal: An Enhancement of Item Based Collaborative Filtering Applied on Online Tutoring Services

REFFERENCES

 Dr. Dan Michael Cortez - Chairman of CET Computer Science department, Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Maynila - dmacortez@plm.edu.ph